export default {
  title: 'French Expressions | French - English',
  description: 'French expressions available for free to beginners up to advanced users.',
  cards: [
    {
      front: 'il ne rêve que d’argent et de plaisirs',
      back:'he only dreams of money and pleasure'
    },
    {
      front: 'je me suis cassé un ongle',
      back:'I broke one of my fingernails'
    },
    {
      front: 'ils restent à l’école le plus longtemps possible',
      back:'they remain at school as long as possible'
    },
    {
      front: 'tout le monde veut être beau',
      back:'everybody wants to be beautiful'
    },
    {
      front: 'et les larmes se remirent à couler',
      back:'and the tears started flowing again'
    },
    {
      front: 'je suis retournée en Espagne en septembre',
      back:'I returned to Spain in September'
    },
    {
      front: 'on était six donc tu peux pas avoir une conversation',
      back:'there were six of us so you can’t have a conversation'
    },
    {
      front: 'c’est un soldat. mais que fait-il ici?',
      back:'it’s a soldier. but what’s he doing here?'
    },
    {
      front: 'elle jouait pour gagner',
      back:'she played to win'
    },
    {
      front: 'je reviendrai dans dix minutes',
      back:'I will return in 10 minutes'
    }
  ]
}
